Finding Aid for Alumni Association (University of Michigan) records, 1845-2001
Bentley Historical Library
- Audio-Visual Materials, 1960-1994; undated
  - Videotapes (VHS), 1988-1998
    - Glissman, Richard L., and Gail Rector
      - A History of Hill Auditorium, #221, 08/09/1993 (Box 162)
    - Glissman, Richard L.
      - The University of Michigan Campus Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow, #165, 07/07/1992 (Box 162)
    - Groat, Linda
      - A Guided Tour of City Form, #51, 06/20/1989 (Box 162)
    - Halstead, Margo
      - The Oldest Form of Heavy Metal Music: An Introduction to the Carillon, #11, 07/07/1988 (Box 162)
    - Hille, R. Thomas
      - The Benedictine Monastery at Las Condes, Chile: A Morphological Analysis of Architectural Form, #50, 06/21/1989 (Box 162)
    - Hubbell, Kent
      - Architecture: The Current State of the Art, #122, 07/10/1991 (Box 162)
    - Jackson, John E.
      - Understanding Economic Change, #73, 04/10/1990 (Box 162)
    - Kirkpatrick, Diane M.
      - The Fair View: Representations of the World's Colombian Exposition of 1893, #235, 11/24/1993 (Box 163)
    - Kish, George
      - Collecting Old Maps, #4, 06/15/1988 (Box 163)
    - Marans, Robert W.
      - UM Urban and Regional Planning Program Initiatives in Detroit and South Africa, #276, 11/15/1994 (Box 163)
    - Marzolf, Marion T.
      - Swedes in Michigan, #184, 08/17/1992 (Box 163)
    - Meadows, Guy A.
      - Great Lakes Coastal Erosion, #153, 06/11/1992 (Box 163)
    - Morton, Harrison L.
      - Nichols Arboretum: Polishing a Crown Jewel, #163, 07/06/1992 (Box 163)
      - Urban Trees Evaluation and Litigation, #183, 08/17/1992 (Box 163)
    - Oksenberg, Michel
      - Reflections of Sino-American Relations, #34, 04/12/1998 (Box 163)
    - Pedraza, Silvia
      - American Transformed: Changing American Society and Its Social Science Research, #251, 06/20/1994 (Box 163)
    - Richstone, Douglas O.
      - Black Holes and the Space Telescope, #263, 07/15/1994 (Box 163)
    - Riggs, Donald E.
      - The Changing Library, #123, 07/10/1991 (Box 163)
    - Schwartz, Ira M.
      - Being Raised by Government: An Inside Look at Michigan's Child Welfare System, #214, 07/29/1993 (Box 163)
    - Smith, Gene
      - Across Two continents: The U-M's Solar Car Team, #179, 08/11/1992 (Box 163)
    - Spink, Walter
      - The Excavations at Ajanta: The Apogee of India's Golden Age, #206, 06/23/1993 (Box 163)
    - Steneck, Nicholas H.
      - Michigan's Tradition in the Health Sciences, #86, 7/9/1990 (Box 163)
    - Teske, Richard G.
      - What Are They Doing on Top of That Mountain?, #89, (pt. 1), 07/31/1990 (Box 163)
      - What Are They Doing on Top of That Mountain?, #90, (pt. 2), 07/31/1990 (Box 163)
    - Thornton, J. Mills
      - Civil Rights Come to Selma, #234, 11/17/1993 (Box 163)
    - Vinovskis, Maris
      - Early Childhood Education: Then and Now, #266, 08/08/1994 (Box 163)
    - Vorus, William S.
      - The Michigan Sea Grant Program, #217, 8/04/1993 (Box 163)
    - Werling, Donn Paul
      - Jens Jensen: Design Approaches for Idealized Works of Nature, #243, 6/7/1994 (Box 163)
    - Wilkinson, Bruce H.
      - Waves, Beaches, and Michigan Shorelines, #262, 07/14/1994 (Box 163)
    - "Black Alumni Reunion", October 1986; 1 video recordings (U-matic) (Box 171)
    - Black Student Recruitment slide show -"A Chance to Achieve", April 1988 (Box 171)
      (Transcript located within "Minority Recruitment Program-Miscellaneous" folder)
    - Dr. Leonard F. Sain Award Recipient-Dr. Alexa Canady, September 1990 (Box 171)
      Biographical video
- Photographs, Circa 1869-1997
  The Photographs series (boxes 134-147; and 169-170) include photographs of various reunion groups (box 134). The photographs are organized by schools and colleges and thereunder chronologically. Classes from 1869 through the 1930s are represented here.
  Also included are photographs from the Michigan Alumnus-additional reunion photographs are located within Subjects file. Other photographs include publicity photos from News and Information News Services and UNITAS; the Reunion of Black Graduates annual meetings (1st, 13th, and 20th), notable African American alumni including Dr. Alexa Canady (the first American woman and first African American to become a neurosurgeon), as well as other reunions and miscellaneous photographs.
  - Class Reunions, 1869-1958
    - Architecture Classes, 1924-1927; 1930; 1952 (Box 134)
    - Business Administration Classes, 1928-1934 (Box 134)
    - Dental Classes, 1882-1954
      - 1882-1889 (Box 134)
      - 1900-1909 (Box 134)
      - 1910-1919 (Box 134)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 134)
      - 1930-1954 (Box 134)
    - Dental Hygienists (Box 134)
      (1955 and 1960 reunions)
    - Engineering Classes, 1904-1947
      - 1904-1909 (Box 134)
      - 1910-1920 (Box 134)
      - 1921-1929 (Box 134)
      - 1931-1947 (Box 134)
    - Law Classes, 1878-1953
      - 1878-1899 (Box 134)
      - 1900-1909 (Box 134)
      - 1910-1920 (Box 134)
      - 1921-1929 (Box 134)
      - 1930-1953 (Box 134)
    - Literary Classes, 1869-1949
      - 1869-1979 (Box 134)
      - 1880-1889 (Box 134)
      - 1890-1898 (Box 134)
      - 1900-1909 (Box 134)
      - 1910-1919 (Box 134)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 134)
      - 1930-1949 (Box 134)
    - Medical Classes, 1872-1952
      - 1872-1899 (Box 134)
      - 1900-1909 (Box 134)
      - 1910-1919 (Box 134)
      - 1921-1929 (Box 134)
      - 1930-1952 (Box 134)
        (scattered years)
    - Nursing Classes, 1903-1958
      - 1903-1916 (Box 134)
      - 1921-1958 (Box 134)
    - Pharmacy Classes, 1881-1937 (scattered dates) (Box 134)
  - Miscellaneous Reunions, 1923-1955
    - Emeritus Club, 1931-1955; 1973 (Box 134)
    - Junior Engineers, 1923 (Box 134)
    - Tappan Classes, 1930 (Box 134)
  - Michigan Alumnus Magazine files
    The series Photographs: Michigan Alumnus Magazine files consists of photographic prints taken for, or acquired by, the magazine. Many were printed in the Alumnus magazine. The photos range form 1x2-inch to 8x10 prints, nearly all of them black and white. The photos are organized into several groups: University Buildings, Non-University Buildings, Subjects; and Individuals.
    - University Buildings
      University Buildings (Boxes 135-136) includes both exterior and interior photos of buildings on the Ann Arbor campus and off-campus university buildings. Many photos of building construction are found here. The interior photos generally show the activities that took place in the buildings, and so overlap the Subjects subseries below.
      - Alexander G. Ruthven Museums Building (Box 135)
      - Alumni Memorial Hall
        - Exterior (Box 135)
        - Interior [includes Alumni Association offices and Art Museum] (Box 135)
      - Angell Hall
        - Aerial views (Box 135)
        - Construction and models (Box 135)
        - Details (Box 135)
        - Exterior (Box 135)
        - Interior [includes lobby and Hopwood Room] (Box 135)
      - Arboretum and Botanical Gardens (Box 135)
      - Architecture Building [exterior and interior, including studios and library] (Box 135)
      - Athletic Administration Building (Box 135)
      - Barbour and Waterman Gymnasiums (Box 135)
      - Beal Residence (Psychopathic Hospital) (Box 135)
      - Buildings and Grounds and Storehouse (Box 135)
      - Burton Memorial Tower (Box 135)
      - Business Administration Building [includes classrooms and library] (Box 135)
      - C. S. Mott Children's Hospital (Box 135)
      - Central Campus, aerial views (Box 135)
      - Central Energy Plant and Substation (Box 135)
      - Chemistry Building (Box 135)
      - Children's Psychiatric Hospital (Box 135)
      - Chrysler Center for Continuing Engineering Education (Box 135)
      - Clarence C. Little Science Building (Box 135)
      - Coliseum (Box 135)
      - College of Pharmacy Building (Box 135)
      - Contagious Disease Hospital (Box 135)
      - Convalescent Ward (Box 135)
      - Crisler Arena [interior] (Box 135)
      - David M. Denison Physics and Astronomy Building (Box 135)
      - Dearborn Campus (Box 135)
      - Dental Building (1891-1908) (Box 135)
      - Dental Building (Built 1908)
        - Exterior (Box 135)
        - Interior [includes dental clinics] (Box 135)
      - Dormitories
        - Adelia Cheever House (Box 135)
        - Alice Crocker Lloyd Hall (Box 135)
        - Betsy Barbour House (Box 135)
        - Couzens Hall (Box 135)
        - East Quadrangle [includes construction and rooms] (Box 135)
        - Fletcher Hall (Box 135)
        - Helen Newberry Residence (Box 135)
        - Martha Cook Building (Box 135)
        - Mary Bartron Henderson House (Box 135)
        - Mary Markley Hall (Box 135)
        - Mosher-Jordan Hall
          - Architect's plans (Box 135)
          - Exterior [includes construction] (Box 135)
          - Interior (Box 135)
        - Oxford Houses (Box 135)
        - South Quadrangle [includes construction and rooms] (Box 135)
        - Stockwell Hall [includes rooms] (Box 135)
        - Victor C. Vaughan House [includes kitchen and rooms] (Box 135)
        - West Quadrangle [includes kitchen and rooms] (Box 135)
      - East Engineering Building [includes laboratories] (Box 135)
      - East Hall [interior only] (Box 135)
      - Economics Building (Box 135)
      - Edward Henry Kraus Natural Science Building (Box 135)
      - Ferry Field (Box 135)
      - Fleming Administration Building (Box 135)
      - Flint Campus (Box 135)
      - Food Service Building [later called Neuroscience Building] (Box 135)
      - Ford Nuclear Reactor [interior only] (Box 135)
      - G. G. Brown Laboratory (Box 135)
      - Golf Clubhouse (Box 135)
      - Harlan Hatcher Graduate Library
        - Exterior [includes construction] (Box 135)
        - Interior (Box 135)
      - Harris Hall (Box 135)
      - Harrison M. Randall Laboratory [includes Summer Physics Institute] (Box 135)
      - Haven Hall (Old) [exterior and interior, includes Law Library and fire] (Box 135)
      - Haven and Mason Halls (New) (Box 135)
      - Health Service [includes staff portraits] (Box 135)
      - [Health Service (Old Building) see Museum Annexes] (Box 135)
      - Henry F. Vaughan Public Health Building (Box 135)
      - Henry S. Frieze Building (Box 135)
      - Hill Auditorium (Box 135)
      - Horace H. Rackham Educational Memorial Building (Detroit) (Box 135)
      - Inglis House (Box 135)
      - Institute for Social Research Building (Box 135)
      - Institute of Science and Technology Building (Box 135)
      - Intramural Sports Building (Box 135)
      - Kelsey Museum of Archaeology (Box 135)
      - Kresge Medical Research Building (Box 135)
      - Lamont-Hussey Observatory (Box 135)
      - Lane Hall (Box 135)
      - Laundry [interiors only] (Box 135)
      - Law Quadrangle (Box 135)
      - Library (built 1883) (Box 135)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts Building (Box 135)
      - Lorch Hall (Box 135)
      - McMath-Hulbert Observatory (Box 135)
      - Mason Hall (Old) (Box 135)
      - [Mason Hall (New) see Haven and Mason Halls] (Box 135)
      - Medical Building (Built 1850) (Box 135)
      - Medical Center (Box 135)
      - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 135)
      - Michigan Children's Institute (Box 135)
      - Michigan League (Box 135)
      - Michigan Stadium [includes construction] (Box 135)
      - Michigan Union
        - Exterior (Box 135)
        - Interior [includes student activities] (Box 135)
        - University Club (Box 135)
      - Mimes Theater Building (Box 135)
      - Morris Hall (Box 135)
      - Mortimer E. Cooley Building (Box 135)
      - Museum Annexes (Box 135)
      - Neuropsychiatric Institute (Box 135)
      - [Neuroscience Building see Food Service Building] (Box 135)
      - North Campus (Box 135)
      - North Hall (Box 135)
      - North Outpatient Building (Veterans' Readjustment Center) (Box 135)
      - Northwood Apartments (Box 135)
      - Observatory (Box 135)
      - Outpatient Clinic (Box 135)
      - Palmer Field (Box 135)
      - Phoenix Memorial Laboratory (Box 135)
      - Portage Lake Observatory (Box 135)
      - Power Center for the Performing Arts (Box 135)
      - President's House (Box 135)
      - Rackham Building (Box 135)
      - Residential College (Proposed) (Box 135)
      - Romance Languages Building (Box 135)
      - Samuel Trask Dana Natural Resources Building (Box 136)
      - School of Education Building, with University Elementary School (Box 136)
        (includes elementary classrooms and construction)
      - School of Music Building (Maynard Street) (Box 136)
      - School of Music Building (North Campus) (Box 136)
      - Simpson Memorial Institute (Box 136)
      - South College [includes fire, 1913] (Box 136)
      - Student Activities Building (Box 136)
      - Student Publications Building (Box 136)
        (includes student publications activities)
      - Substation (near Barbour and Waterman Gymnasiums) (Box 136)
      - Synchrotron (Box 136)
      - Tappan Hall (Box 136)
      - Tunnels (Box 136)
        (includes construction)
      - Undergraduate Library (Box 136)
      - University Hall [includes demolition] (Box 136)
      - University Hospital (Built 1925) (Box 136)
      - University Press Building (Box 136)
      - University Terrace Apartments (Box 136)
      - Veterans' Readjustment Center (Box 136)
        (see North Outpatient Building)
      - Veterans Village (Box 136)
      - W. K. Kellogg Foundation Institute (Box 136)
      - Walter E. Lay Automotive Laboratory (Box 136)
      - West Physics Building (Box 136)
      - William L. Clements Library (Box 136)
      - Willow Run Airport (Box 136)
      - Willow Run Research Center (Box 136)
      - Willow Village (Box 136)
      - Women's Athletic Building (Forest, now Washtenaw, Avenue) (Box 136)
      - Women's Athletic Building (State Street) (Box 136)
      - Women's Hospital (Box 136)
      - Yost Ice Arena (Yost Field House) (Box 136)
    - Non-University Buildings
      Non-University Buildings (Box 136) is primarily fraternity and sorority houses, although it also includes some other Ann Arbor buildings, such as Joe Parker's Place and Prettyman's, and a few non-Ann Arbor topics.
      - Alpha Chi Omega (Box 136)
      - Alpha Rho Chi (Box 136)
      - Alpha Chi Sigma (Box 136)
      - Alpha Phi (Box 136)
      - Alpha Tau Omega (Box 136)
      - Alpha Xi Delta (Box 136)
      - American University Union, Paris, circa 1918 (Box 136)
      - Ann Arbor Inn [construction] (Box 136)
      - Chi Psi (Box 136)
      - Collegiate Sorosis (Box 136)
      - Delta Delta Delta (Box 136)
      - Delta Kappa Epsilon (Box 136)
      - Delta Sigma Delta (Box 136)
      - Delta Tau Delta (Box 136)
      - Delta Theta Phi (Box 136)
      - Delta Upsilon (Box 136)
      - Detroit, Mich. buildings (Box 136)
      - Frankfort, Mich. lighthouses (Box 136)
      - Fraternity/sorority houses, unidentified (Box 136)
      - Hillel (Box 136)
      - Joe Parker's (Box 136)
      - Kappa Alpha Theta (Box 136)
      - Kappa Kappa Gamma (Box 136)
      - Kappa Sigma (Box 136)
      - Michigan Central Railroad Station, Ann Arbor (Box 136)
      - Phi Beta Pi (Box 136)
      - Phi Chi (Box 136)
      - Phi Delta Phi (Box 136)
      - Phi Delta Theta (Box 136)
      - Phi Kappa (Box 136)
      - Phi Kappa Psi (Box 136)
      - Phi Rho Sigma (Box 136)
      - Pi Kappa Alpha (Box 136)
      - Prettyman's (Box 136)
      - Psi Upsilon (Box 136)
      - Sigma Phi (Box 136)
      - Theta Chi (Box 136)
      - Theta Delta Chi (Box 136)
      - Theta Kappa Psi (Box 136)
      - Theta Xi (Box 136)
      - Triangle (Box 136)
      - WJR transmitter (Box 136)
      - Xi Psi Phi (Box 136)
      - Zeta Psi (Box 136)
    - Subjects
      Subjects (Boxes 136-138) primarily includes student and alumni activities at the University, especially sports, reunions, and commencements. This subseries overlaps the University Buildings subseries, which also includes some activities, and the Individuals subseries below, which includes photos of the activities of notable figures at the University.
      - Alumnae Council (Box 136)
      - Alumnae groups
        - A-M (Box 136)
        - N-Z (Box 136)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 136)
      - Alumni Association (Box 136)
      - Alumni groups
        - Districts (Box 136)
        - A-Bi (Box 136)
        - Bl-Bu (Box 136)
        - C (Box 136)
        - D-E (Box 136)
        - F-G (Box 136)
        - H (Box 136)
        - I-L (Box 136)
        - M (Box 136)
        - N-R (Box 136)
        - Sa-Sc (Box 136)
        - Se-Sy (Box 136)
        - T-Z (except Washington) (Box 136)
        - Washington
          - Before, 1959 (Box 136)
          - Or later, 1959 (Box 136)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Before World War II (Box 136)
          - World War II or later (Box 136)
          - Unidentified (Box 136)
      - Alumni Press (Box 136)
      - Alumni Triennial, 2nd, 1928 (Box 136)
      - Alumni University (Box 136)
      - Ann Arbor, Miscellaneous views (Box 136)
      - Audio-visual (Box 136)
      - Automobiles (Box 136)
      - Aviation (Box 136)
      - Baird Carillon (Box 136)
      - Band
        - Marching (Box 136)
        - On the field (football)
          - 1930-1950 (Box 136)
          - And later, 1950 (Box 136)
          - Undated (Box 136)
        - Trip, 1961 (Box 136)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 136)
      - Boy Scouts (Box 137)
      - Broadcast: Pontiac "Varsity Show" on NBC, January 22, 1937 (Box 137)
      - Broadcasting (Box 137)
      - Bus stop (Box 137)
      - Business Office, University (Box 137)
      - Camps (Box 137)
      - Campus views
        - Landscape and monuments (Box 137)
        - People (Box 137)
        - Winter (Box 137)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 137)
      - Celebration, 1937 (Box 137)
      - Class Day (Box 137)
      - Class games (Box 137)
      - Classes
        - Pre-1910, undated (Box 137)
        - 1910-1919 (Box 137)
        - 1920-1929 (Box 137)
        - 1930-1939 (Box 137)
        - 1940-1949 (Box 137)
        - 1950-1960 (Box 137)
      - Commencement
        - A (Box 137)
        - B (Box 137)
        - C (Box 137)
        - 1924-1929 (Box 137)
        - 1930-1936 (Box 137)
        - 1937-1950 (Box 137)
        - 1951-1969 (Box 137)
        - 1964 (Box 137)
          (President Johnson)
        - 1970 (Box 137)
      - Communists (Box 137)
      - Dance recitals (Box 137)
      - Dances and parties, Student (Box 137)
      - Development Council (Box 137)
      - Dramatics
        - Junior Girls' Play (Box 137)
        - Play Production (Box 137)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 137)
      - Engineering
        - Daylight Lighting Lab (Box 137)
        - Streamlined train (Box 137)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 137)
      - Exhibits (Box 137)
      - Expeditions and excavations
        - Greenland (Box 137)
        - Near East (Box 137)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 137)
      - Faculty (Groups) (Box 137)
      - Foreign students: Cosmopolitan Club and miscellaneous groups (Box 137)
      - Fraternity and sorority life (Box 137)
      - Gilbert and Sullivan Society (Box 137)
      - Girls' State (Box 137)
      - Homecoming (Box 137)
      - Honors program (Box 137)
      - Hospitals, interiors and people (Box 137)
      - Huron River (Box 137)
      - Legislators (Box 137)
      - Literary College centennial and conference (Box 137)
      - "M" Club (Box 137)
      - Men's Glee Club (Box 137)
      - Michigamua (Box 137)
      - Michigan Daily (Box 137)
      - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 137)
      - Michigan Week (Box 137)
      - Military
        - Informal shots (Box 137)
        - Judge Advocate General's School (Box 137)
        - R.O.T.C (Box 137)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 137)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Old pictures (Box 137)
          (includes photo of peony garden ca. 1920s)
        - Or later, 1940s (Box 137)
        - June 1971 issue (Box 137)
        - November 1971 issue (Box 137)
        - Unidentified issue, ca. 1971 (Box 137)
      - Missile research (Box 137)
      - Movie about university life, 1927 (Box 137)
      - Musical organizations and activities (Box 137)
        (see also Band, Men's Glee Club)
      - Natural Resources (Box 137)
      - Navy (Box 137)
      - Nurses (Box 137)
      - Orientation, Student (Box 137)
      - Polio vaccine announcement (Box 137)
      - Political Science (Box 137)
      - President's office (Box 137)
      - Project Michigan (Box 137)
      - Public Administration, Institute of (Box 137)
      - Radio telescope (Box 137)
      - Regents (Box 137)
      - Registration (Box 137)
      - Research
        (see also Engineering, Expeditions, Missile research, Project Michigan)
        - Biological (Box 137)
        - Mount Sinai (Box 137)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 137)
      - Reunions
        - Group A (undated)
          - Formal large groups (Box 137)
          - Informal small groups (Box 137)
          - Or later, 1940s (Box 137)
        - Group B (dated) (Box 138)
          - 1900-1930s (Box 138)
          - 1942-1945 (Box 138)
          - 1946 (Box 138)
            (Victory)
          - 1947 (Box 138)
          - 1948 (Box 138)
          - 1949 (Box 138)
          - 1950 (Box 138)
          - 1951 (Box 138)
          - 1952 (Box 138)
          - 1953 (Box 138)
          - 1954 (Box 138)
          - 1955 (Box 138)
          - 1956 (Box 138)
          - 1957 (Box 138)
          - 1958 (Box 138)
          - 1959 (Box 138)
          - 1960 (Box 138)
          - 1961-1965 (Box 138)
      - Ruthven ten-year celebration (Box 138)
      - Sault Ste. Marie Locks (Box 138)
      - Scholarships and fellowships (Box 138)
      - Sesquicentennial (Box 138)
      - Sports, Coed
        - Ice skating (Box 138)
        - Rifle (Box 138)
        - Skiing (Box 138)
        - Tobogganing (Box 138)
      - Sports, Men's
        - Archery (Box 138)
        - Baseball (Box 138)
        - Basketball (Box 138)
        - Boxing (Box 138)
        - Cheerleaders (Box 138)
        - Cross country (Box 138)
        - Fencing (Box 138)
        - Football
          - Undated, 2 envelopes (Box 138)
          - Undated, 1960- (Box 138)
          - 1879-1926 (Box 138)
          - 1928-1932 (Box 138)
          - 1933-1936 (Box 138)
          - 1937-1939 (Box 138)
          - 1940-1941 (Box 138)
          - 1942-1944 (Box 138)
          - 1945-1946 (Box 138)
          - 1947-1948 (Box 138)
          - 1949-1951 (Box 138)
          - 1952-1954 (Box 138)
          - 1955-1956 (Box 138)
          - 1957 (Box 138)
          - 1958 (Box 138)
          - 1960 (Box 138)
          - 1961 (Box 138)
          - 1962-1963 (Box 138)
          - 1966 (Box 138)
          - 1967 (Box 138)
        - Football: Rose Bowl Game
          - 1948 (Box 138)
          - 1951 (Box 138)
          - 1965 (Box 138)
        - Golf (Box 138)
        - Gymnastics (Box 138)
        - Handball (Box 138)
        - Ice hockey (Box 138)
        - Intramural (Box 138)
        - Ping pong (Box 138)
        - Soccer (Box 138)
        - Swimming (Box 138)
        - Tennis (Box 138)
        - Track (Box 138)
        - Volleyball (Box 138)
        - Wrestling (Box 138)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 138)
      - Sports, Women's
        - Archery (Box 138)
        - Badminton (Box 138)
        - Baseball (Box 138)
        - Basketball (Box 138)
        - Bowling (Box 138)
        - Fencing (Box 138)
        - Field hockey (Box 138)
        - Golf (Box 138)
        - Gymnastics (Box 138)
        - Ice hockey (Box 138)
        - Riding (Box 138)
        - Soccer (Box 138)
        - Swimming (Box 138)
        - Tennis (Box 138)
        - Volleyball (Box 138)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 138)
      - State Street (Box 138)
      - Student governors (Box 138)
      - Student life